GET IN TOUCH WITH ME

Mobile: +31(0)642207286 Email: lily@skygliders.nl

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/lilymineur/



INTRODUCTION

Colleagues describe me as outgoing, empathetic, collaborative, and solution-oriented. This is what you can expect me to bring into my work every day.

My journey at Insider represents a pivotal chapter in my professional journey. It has been a transformative learning experience that has significantly expanded my knowledge of the SaaS industry. As a dedicated Customer Success Manager I take pride in becoming a trusted strategic partner within my customers' teams.

In my current role, I am overseeing the complete client lifecycle, from initial onboarding through to daily support, formulating tailored strategies, reporting and expansion. Internally, I collaborate with the development teams and join the product sprints to facilitate ongoing product enhancements.

Throughout my career, I have consistently established strong relationships and have been moved into roles with added responsibilities. The additional challenge that this brings is something I have always thrived on and delivered against.

HIGHLIGHTS

Skilled in Gainsight, Jira, and Power BI Google Analytics 4 Certificate Developing strategies based on client objectives International experience

LANGUAGES

Dutch: Native speaker English: Fluent Spanish: B1 degree

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

Outdoor sports Immersive events Exploring new cities Visiting modern art museums

LILY MINEUR

Customer Success Manager at Insider (SaaS)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Success Manager

Insider, Amsterdam | March 2022 - Current

- Client portfolio: Enterprise clients in e-commerce worth €1.4M in ARR across both the Benelux and UK market
- **Stakeholders**: CMO, Marketing Director, CRM Project manager, UX and Optimisation, Development department
- KPI Elements: MRR incl. 10% expansion, NPS, Product Usage, POC Closing, Personal development
- KPI Performance: Targets always achieved
- Coaching: 3 new CSM's in their first 6 months at Insider

Account Manager

Adform, Amsterdam | December 2020 - February 2022

- Managing day to day relationships with my client portfolio who work with (one or more of) our products: TPAS, DCO, DSP, SSP and DMP
- Understand client's business and continuously help them improve their online campaign performance
- Constantly seeking upsell and cross-sell opportunities to increase the revenue

Online Marketing Specialist

iChoosr, Amsterdam | June 2018 - November 2020

- B2C paid online advertising strategies across GDN, DV360 and Facebook
- Data analysis: Google Tag Manager and Analytics
- UX: Influence framework, customer journey mapping, persona creation
- Project Management: overseeing projects with both internal & external stakeholders across UK, USA and Japan

Digital Account Manager

Collective/ Time Inc., London | November 2017 - April 2018

- Responsible for the daily management and growth across WPP agencies
- Increase client base by meeting and onboarding new accounts
- Maximise revenue growth by seeking new opportunities

Account Executive

Mindshare UK, London | March 2016 - October 2017

- Media buyer traded team
- Negotiate and purchase media campaigns
- Overseeing entire campaign set up: planning, booking, trafficking, reporting
- Responsible for client budgets
- Retain quality control to meet media plan objectives and present performance

EDUCATION

Master of Business Administration

University of Amsterdam (UvA), graduated in 2015

Pre-master Business Administration

University of Amsterdam (UvA), graduated in 2014

Bachelor Communication Science

VU University of Amsterdam, graduated in 2013

Media and Entertainment Management

University INHolland, Haarlem, foundation course, 2010